Reo...
Yuka.
You've grown taller.
I guess so.
Reo, who is this?
Yuka Oihara,
a senior from middle school.
Nice to meet you.
[Yuka Oihara: Reo's senior from middle school. Taught him basketball, and winner of their middle school's beauty pageant]
This is Kasu—
Mai Toda.
She's my girlfriend.
Nice to meet you.
I see. What a cute girlfriend.
Wow, what a coincidence!
No interrupting them, Ikumi.
- Ken?
- Whoa,
Yuka?
You haven't changed in these two years.
Y-You weren't meeting up with Reo, right?
We just ran into each other. I was surprised.
You returned from Kagoshima?
Yes, I have some business here. I'm going back in a week.
I see. Why Kagoshima?
I'm attending university there.
Interesting.
Come on, let's go!
Listen, Reo—
Since we're busy, Ritsuki asked me to bring Mai as well.
But it's my day off.
This is cause you guys are slacking.
See you, Yuka.
Take care.
[Ai-Chan's Secret | Episode 8]
So she is your ex!
What were you doing with her, and your current girlfriend?
We just coincidentally met.
"Coincidentally"? Really?
He introduced you as his girlfriend, right?
You'll be fine.
Still, it feels like there's something between them.
You can't help but be curious about an ex.
Yeah...
Reo and Yuka were totally lovey-dovey.
- Kenji.
- That's all in the past.
She's only his ex.
[Part-time Job: Egawatei]
Hello?
Right now?
Sorry we couldn't take it easy.
It's fine.
I've already ended things with Yuka.
Yeah.
Sorry about this, Reo. The manager had business at the other branch.
No worries.
My plans got canceled anyway.
Mai?
- Kasumi?
- Huh?
I see you're worried about his ex-girlfriend.
Not at all.
Isn't she Reo's first?
How can you tell?
Watching them, it's obvious.
If you waver and break, maybe there'll be space for me?
Not a chance.
Where's Hiroko?
She's busy in the office.
More importantly, the phone.
What about a phone?
You should check it.
Why?
His ex-girlfriend may be contacting him.
Are you saying I should look at Reo's phone?
Obviously! What if he is contacting his ex?
He wouldn't.
You're too naive.
There are plenty of girls after him.
Act so lax in this crisis, and you won't qualify as Reo's girlfriend!
Not that I acknowledge you either.
What? A "crisis"?
She's overreacting.
A crisis.
Hiroko?
Hiroko? What's wrong?
The hell do you mean, you "cheated on her"?
- Ouch, what's wrong with you!
- Was your sincerity a lie?
I just went to a mixer as a favor, and my ex—
Your ex-girlfriend?!
Why go, when you have a girlfriend!
It's a misunderstanding! Right now, I'm loyal to Hiroko.
She was crying.
She was?
Hey, are you running?!
I won't forgive any cheating!
An ex-girlfriend? Unforgivable.
[Ramen Egawatei]
[Open for business]
Hello?
I'm glad your phone number is the same.
Yuka?
[Reo]
What is it.
Well...
This afternoon was such a surprise.
It was.
I've held onto this t-shirt
I borrowed from you,
and I want to return it.
Can we meet, just once?
You can throw it out.
- But —
- Sorry.
I'm out of the house right now.
I… see.
In that case, I'll ask another time.
My current girlfriend gets jealous easily,
so I want to end it with this call.
I'm sorry.
See you.
His ex-girlfriend may be contacting him.
[Kafuu High School]
[Call History]
[Delete]
Listen, it's about yesterday...
Sorry I didn't help with the whole Mai and Yuka situation.
- You planned on helping?
- I did.
I did, but… I got all excited.
- Was Mai alright afterwards?
- Yeah.
No need to worry about us.
What's with that confidence? I wasted my time worrying.
Besides, I won't meet with Yuka anymore.
- You've become a real man.
- And you sound high-and-mighty.
Listen, you were in bad shape after Yuka's rejection.
I couldn't watch you spiral.
That's in the past.
Deep down, I was worried.
Thought you'd never fall in love again.
Love's amazing.
Be grateful to Mai.
Hey, how're things going with Morikawa?
Don't ask!
Seriously, don't.
- And then?
- She has no love for me.
Mr. Misato, one more lap, right?
You're dawdling. Two more.
- What?!
- Why is Koike so pissed?
- I wonder—
- Why'd you just stop?
Look, it's Yuka.
Is she the ex-girlfriend?
Yeah.
She is pretty.
- Want to come watch us practice?
- No, I'm just...
I thought you were going to "help out".
Mai is not here, so it should be fine.
Let's go!
You want to watch?
Let's see...
Pardon me.
Hello?
The preschool, now?
Yes, feel free to watch.
What brings you here?
I need to speak to Reo.
- About what?
- Morikawa.
I wanted to speak, face-to-face.
Let's head on out.
Mai, do something.
Why me?
She is Reo's senior. 1 on 1 her in basketball.
- A 1 on 1?
- Exactly, now hurry!
- No thanks, I don't wanna.
- What?!
Yeah, quit while you can.
She's not someone you can win against.
Yuka was Reo's mentor.
So there is no way you would win.
- Nice job, Kenji!
- Nice job to what?
Excuse me.
Go, go, Ai!
My name is Aiko Kasumi.
I'm somewhat of a… rival to Reo.
His rival?
Would you like have a 1 on 1 against me?
What?
You'll play offense.
That's my forte.
Beat her to a pulp!
- She's really good.
- Is she?
How do you feel, seeing your ex and current girlfriend duel?
Shut it.
You won't watch?
Aiko is going to win.
A two year break makes a difference.
Not at all. I became desperate halfway through.
Really?
You're good at the straightforward play style.
Aiko, was it?
Thank you, I had fun.
Same here.
I'm going to wash my hands. Are the sinks that way?
Here you go.
May I? Thank you.
What an innocent smile.
You have guts, coming to see your ex-boyfriend.
Don't just lash out at her.
Reo...
This person is unexpectedly fragile.
That's the wrong person to protect.
Next time you mess up, I won't forgive you.
Where is Reo?
The bathroom?
Let's play a 1 on 1 ourselves.
No, thanks.
Why not?
I wonder where he went.
You didn't come to return the t-shirt, did you?
I'm sorry, that was a lie.
I really wanted to speak with you,
and meet once more.
You're still...
here.
Reo, you linger in my heart.
Even when I transferred schools, and left for university.
I often wonder what would've happened
if we didn't break up.
- That's why I came, and decided if I saw you—
- That's...
already a thing of the past.
I...
seriously love my current girlfriend.
That's why
we won't meet anymore.
Wait, Reo!
I really...
regret
breaking up with you.
You're the one who let go,
Yuka.
- I know, that's why—
- Sorry.
♫ What awaits in this battle of love? ♫
♫ It seems it won't end in a draw ♫
♫ You hated loosing, ♫
♫ So I won't let you go easy on me ♫
You saw an unsightly part of me.
Thank you. You're kind.
♫ The secret that belongs to only us. 1on1 ♫
"Be kind to girls",
that's our family motto.
How manly.
I get told that often.
♫ Rather than touching, we can melt
into one another's embrace ♫
♫ I'll let you get near just to return you like a wave ♫
You still...
love Reo, don't you?
Pathetic, aren't I?
I'm the only one
stuck in the past.
I can't move on.
I feel like a fool.
♫ The bargaining is also clumsy ♫
♫ I can’t beat you all the time ♫
Falling in love with someone...
feels amazing.
Even ordinary sunset bring happiness
when watching them with your crush.
♫ Deeper ♫
Worries easily build up
when they don't contact you.
Jealousy is nonstop,
everything's confusing,
and you can't be honest.
It's all pretty pathetic.
Seriously...
how foolish.
♫ Only I know this ♫
Even so...
♫ Rather than touching, we can melt
into one another's embrace ♫
the feeling of falling in love...
♫ I'll let you get near just to return you like a wave ♫
is something irreplaceable.
♫ I'll steal you away before anyone gets the chance ♫
♫ Lips to exchange ♫
So, you have someone you love, too.
Yeah,
there is someone I like.
I...
love Reo Amano.
[Next time]
- Give up.
- It's not that easy.
She's unexpectedly stubborn.
- I'll cut it clean.
- A battle against his ex?
It's fine if you look uncool.
Yuka, you'll never disappear from within me.
So I thought you'd pick Yuka over me.
I want to break up with Mai.